arcadecabin.com 2016-03-14

# ArcadeCabin.com Privacy Policy

At ArcadeCabin.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is the information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit ArcadeCabin.com, and how we safeguard your information. Please be aware that we will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with third-parties without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. 

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as Comcast or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. These log datas are use for statistical purposes only to improve our site and enhance user's experience. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
A "cookie" is a small piece of data from a website and stored in user's web browser. We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a specific content once in your visit, or the ability to remember your username. 

**E-mail**  
If you subscribe to our newsletter, your e-mail address will be use to send you site updates and other site related issues only. All subscribers may choose to opt out by clicking the unsubscribe link included in our e-mail. If you contact us via our contact form, your email address will only be use to reply to your inquiry. 

**3rd-Party Advertisements**  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Privacy Policy Revision**  
ArcadeCabin.com will from time to time review and revise this privacy policy, any changes will be posted on this website. ArcadeCabin.com has the right to change our privacy practices without prior notice. 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.
